I want to know what future
awaits me, the villainess,
and I want to see how this game ends.
And to do that...
I need to talk to King Pearl once more.
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Love Is Always and Forever
Pearl.
Claire...
I took the form of a woman
because you said you hated men,
but I don't need to anymore, right?
Pearl, no one would condemn a fairy king
for creating a natural disaster.
It's possible that people just
deem them necessary sometimes.
But...
it's not good to involve humans
in a problem between you and me.
Why is it always just me?
It started with the selfish
demands of the sea fairies.
I want Icilla to be happy!
But I would never separate two people
who love each other so deeply.
That's just how it is... but...
when I saw Claire having so much fun
with people other than me...
I always thought that fairy kings
were lonely beings...
but I'm the only one who's lonely.
I'm just fine alone.
Pearl...
I know you long for company
more than anyone else.
King Pearl!
Please pardon our intrusion.
Tiararose. Icilla Pearllant.
What? Are you,
by any chance... King Claire?
Yes. This is my original appearance.
Why have you come here?
I'm here because I want to
see everything through.
Prince Aqua remained on land
so he could take command in
preventing chaos among the populace.
I never would have guessed he'd overcome
the secret elixir's effects himself.
Just who are you?
Who am I?
I'm just a humble villainess.
Of course, I can't tell her that.
But there's one thing I can say.
The only one I love is Prince Aqua.
So there is nothing that you need
to be concerned about.
Love...
How lucky you are.
You have a man who thinks
of you and you alone.
Huh?
The one I desired left me, saying
we were too far apart in standing.
"A human and a fairy king
can never be together."
That's what he said before
choosing a human woman.
He said he didn't want to forget me,
so he took my name.
I have no need for a love
that is neither here nor there.
My name is... Icilla Pearllant...
Does this mean someone among my ancestors
declined marriage with King Pearl?
I had no idea King Pearl endured
such a tragic romance...
That is in the past now.
What is this?
A coral accessory.
I chose it because
I thought it would suit you.
What?
Tiararose taught me that
the woman I love would be happier
with a gift that I chose myself.
I knew it! It suits you perfectly!
Could it be that you
were jealous of Tiararose?
I didn't realize you loved me so much
that you'd blacken the ocean.
I thought it was because you hated me.
O-Of course I don't hate—
But in this case, you need
to understand what you've done
and accept punishment as a fairy king.
Wait a moment!
Could you please allow me
to choose King Pearl's punishment?
I'm sure it'll be lighter
than the punishment
she'd receive from a fairy king.
Icilla Pearllant, I'm afraid
I cannot agree to that.
A human cannot be permitted to
have a say in what happens to Pearl.
Do not think a human can tie Pearl down,
especially one who is
a descendant of Pearllant.
Lady Icilla!
King Claire, Lady Icilla is...
Don't worry. I only
returned her to the surface.
Tiararose, you said you
wanted to see all this through.
For that reason, I will allow your
presence here until the very end.
Th-Thank you.
And? What is my punishment?
I'm glad you're accepting it
gracefully, Pearl.
What happened was my own fault.
In that case,
give Aquasteed and Tiararose
the blessing of the Sea Fairy King.
That's the punishment
I've come up with for you.
What kind of joke is that?!
I've made up my mind never to
give my blessing to any humans!
Well, I'm quite fond of the
Kingdom of Marinforest, you know.
The Sky Fairy King
has blessed the crown prince,
and his consort has the
Forest Fairy King on her side.
So if the Sea Fairy King
would also bless them both,
this kingdom would have peace.
So bless them with all your might, okay?
But if I do that, it will nearly
deplete my magic power!
Yes. That's what makes it a punishment.
It's a punishment, and it
helps this kingdom flourish.
Everyone wins!
Claire... You like this kingdom
a bit too much.
But if that is what you desire...
Ocean of ripples and waves,
bestow the highest of blessings
upon the two
who shoulder the future of Marinforest.
For Aquasteed Marinforest,
a water blade that can pierce all...
and for Tiararose Lapis Marinforest,
a water wall that can deflect all.
I feel so hot!
Tiararose, try to relax.
You just need to take in Pearl's power.
There doesn't seem to be any mass chaos.
Yes, thankfully, there weren't very many
people who personally saw the black ocean.
That's good. I'll travel
around the city just in ca—
What is it?
It's the blessing of the Sea Fairy King.
Claire mentioned it before,
but this impact...
Tiara must be receiving it, too.
Elliot, I'm heading back!
Prince Aquasteed!
Tiara...
I'm exhausted.
I'm so glad you're all right.
Welcome back, Prince Aqua.
Are you all right, Tiara?
You received the Sea Fairy
King's blessing, right?
You don't feel unwell?
No, it did take me by surprise,
but I'm not unwell in any way.
Thank goodness.
P-Prince Aqua...
Prince Aquasteed, Lady Tiararose...
I am sincerely sorry for causing
so many problems for the two of you.
Please punish me as you see fit.
The punishment for Pearl,
the Sea Fairy King,
was decided by Claire, the Sky Fairy King.
I received the blessing
of the ocean's protection.
I received an attack-focused blessing.
I have always overseen
the seas and beaches,
but I see that is no longer needed.
Because the two of you have received
the Sea Fairy King's blessing.
No, I'd like you to continue
managing the ocean.
What?
You know it better
than anyone else, after all.
I agree.
But I...
You're the right one
for the job. After all...
there's no one who loves
the ocean as much as you do.
That's what I think.
Tiara has the forest to look after,
so she won't have time
to oversee the ocean.
We'll have increased
diplomatic relations, as well.
I don't want to be at the mercy
of the fairy kings any longer.
I guess he wants me to stay at
the castle and not go to the sea.
Before, I never would have
even imagined this happening.
I'm sure she only agreed to use
the elixir in a moment of weakness.
Either that, or it's just
the power of the game.
Sometimes I suspect that what the game
mandates is just what someone wants,
and that worries me, but still...
If that is what the two of you desire,
then I humbly accept.
We'll be counting on you, Lady Icilla.
I guess that's case closed for now.
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Huh? I can't mo—
He usually wakes up before I do.
This is rare.
His eyelashes are so long.
I love him.
I brought you flowers.
K-K-Keith! Why are you in our bedroom?!
Do fairy kings know nothing
of common courtesy?!
What's this?
Does the crown prince of this kingdom
not believe that fairy kings are absolute?
I will not compromise
when it comes to Tiara.
I'm the only one allowed to see her
when she first wakes up!
Heh. What a selfish crown prince you are.
I don't need that from a fairy king
who enters a married couple's
bedroom without permission!
If you have business with us, wait in
another room until we've changed clothes!
Right, right.
It's sugar gathered from your flowers.
You brought that much sugar?!
Also, it's only a tiny bit,
but you can gather their nectar, too.
Even nectar?!
And the petals are also edible.
It really is your flower, Tiara.
They have a faint sweetness.
I'd expect nothing less of Tiara's flower.
Every part of it is sweet, just like her.
You're the only one who
would describe me as sweet.
As much as I enjoy watching Tiara,
could you do that somewhere else?
With these, maybe I can
make a new dessert!
I'll try a taste first.
The sweet, gentle flavor fills my mouth.
Maybe a hard candy?
Now for some water.
Maybe... if I dig deep into my magic...
I did it! It worked!
Once they're a lovely golden color,
I'll wrap them in petals,
cool them, and...
they're done!
What are these sweets called?
Tortoiseshell candies.
They're so pretty,
and they look delicious!
Thank you, Philine!
Let's take them to Prince Aqua right away.
His Highness is on the beach supervising
the transplanting of your trees.
Prince Aqua!
Tiara!
What brings you here?
The new sweets I made are done,
so I brought them for you.
They're tortoiseshell candies.
I wanted you to be
the first one to try them.
They're a lot like you.
Huh?
Beautiful, cute, and tasty-looking.
P-Prince Aqua, aren't you
still in the middle of work?
We'll take our time
when I'm finished, then.
King Claire...
I was looking at the ocean.
I was so moved the first time
I saw the ocean in Marinforest.
I couldn't believe it was so pretty.
It looks so beautiful because
it's King Pearl's ocean, of course.
Some days will be sunny,
and others stormy with cold rain.
This ocean is King Pearl's
loving heart itself.
That's why it touches the heart so much.
I love King Pearl's ocean.
I'd like to give some of these
tortoiseshell candies to her.
Eating delicious sweets
always cheers me up.
I hope these will calm her soul,
even if only a little bit.
Tiararose...
Oh, I'm sorry, Prince Aqua!
After I just said I wanted you
to eat them first...
Should I not?
Tiara... You are too cute.
P-Prince Aqua...
It's all right.
You can do as you like.
Thank you!
This is...
The beach is regenerating!
King Claire, what is this?
It's Pearl's power.
This is a farewell gift from me.
King Pearl!
Pearl has given her blessing to the ocean
using the last bit
of magic she had left.
She used up all her magic...
...and went into a deep sleep.
Honestly...
Now there's no way to know
who's really being punished.
That dummy.
King Claire...
Tiararose, could you give me
the sweets intended for Pearl?
Of course.
I'm hoping it will reach her this way.
I pray for blessings
upon King Pearl's future.
Prince Aquasteed and Lady Tiararose.
I hear you've both received blessings
from the Sea Fairy King.
Now Marinforest's future is secure!
Lady Tiararose, you look like a goddess.
Thank you. I feel so happy and reassured.
What was that?
What is it? I feel like
something's calling for me...
This is... a letter from Lady Akari.
She's written all about her happy days
with Prince Hartknights in Japanese.
That's so like Lady Akari.
By the way, Lady Tiara,
is everything going well
between you and Prince Aqua?
If the sequel's heroine tries
to pull anything, don't give in!
And watch out for the love
potion event, especially!
Lady Akari... I wish you'd
sent this letter a bit sooner.
So that really was an event in the game.
Once you receive
the Fairy King's blessings,
you unlock a hidden stage!
Have you done that yet?
A hidden stage?
She writes about what
will happen from here.
If I know what's going to happen,
maybe I can avoid the game's adjustments
and secure a happy future.
But...
I found you.
I've been looking for you, Tiara.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
You seem a bit uneasy.
Tiara, never forget
that I will always be by your side.
In sickness and in health.
And I want to share all of your joy,
sadness, and pain with you.
For as long as I live.
Prince Aqua...
Tiara?
I love you. I love you so much.
I love you with all my heart.
Thank you so much for choosing me.
I'm so happy to be with you,
Prince Aqua... no, Aqua.
Oh, darn it... You are just too cute.
Would you dance with me?
With pleasure.
There's no way the story of a villainess
who's adored by the prince
of a neighboring kingdom
exists in the game.
But no matter what sort of story unfolds,
as long as I'm with Prince Aqua...
I'm happy.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Rebecca Cottrill
Mariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
I'm back.
Welcome home.